Regardless of which type of networking event you attend, the number one thing
どんなタイプの交流会に参加するのであっても すべての人にわかってもらえる一番大事なことは
that will help you navigate all of them is having a great elevator pitch.
優れたエレベータピッチ (簡潔な自己紹介) を することです
Elevator pitches were originally known as sales pitches and
エレベータピッチは 元々セールストークとして知られ
lived solely in the business world.
ビジネスの世界のみのものでした
However, they soon became popular across all industries because it was a way for
でもすぐにすべての業界で 評判になりました
people to quickly communicate the purpose and value of something.
それは 人が何かの目的と価値を 素早く伝える方法だったからです
Having a elevator pitch is invaluable in your career development.
エレベータピッチを用意しておくことは 皆さんのキャリア計画でとても大切なことです
These short sentences will find their way in your LinkedIn summaries,
この短い文章は 皆さんの LinkedIn のプロフィールや
in talking to a recruiter, in small talk with friends, or
採用担当者との会話 友人とのおしゃべり
in requesting a promotion.
また昇進願の中で活躍します
Elevator pitches also help outside of networking, such as in a job interview,
エレベータピッチは 交流会以外の 就職面接などで社員から
when the employer asks you why you're applying or what you're interested in.
応募の動機や興味があることを 尋ねられるときにも役立ちます
I have to admit that I did not like my first experience with elevator pitches.
私のエレベータピッチの最初の経験は よいものではなかったことは認めざるをえません
I was at a professional development event and was put in with a group
私は職能開発イベントに参加していて 知らない人たちのグループにいました
of strangers, and we all had to respond to the prompt, tell me about yourself.
そして全員が自己紹介を すばやくしなければなりませんでした
I was first.
私がトップバッターでした
I rambled.
私はだらだらと話しました
I've locked a lot of that experience from my memory, but
この経験は記憶から 消し去りたいのですが
I'm sure I sounded like this, hi, I'm Trinh.
たぶんこんな感じだったのは確かです こんにちは トリンです
I grew up in the San Francisco Bay Area, and I go to school.
私はサンフランシスコベイエリアで育って 学校に行っています
And I'm interested in education, but I've never worked in education.
教育に興味がありますが 教育業界で働いたことはありません
And yeah, that's why I'm here today, to help me make that transition.
今日はここに来て 何か変わればと思っています
I was really embarrassed.
本当に恥ずかしかったです
Especially when everyone else gave their answers and
特に 自分以外のみんなが 答えていたときに
it sounded like they had their life together.
その人たちが一緒に生活してきたように 聞こえました
But it was also a great learning experience because after hearing myself,
でも これはとてもためになる経験でもありました 自分自身の答えを聞いた後に
I kept thinking, why do I need to tell people where I grew up?
私が育った場所を話す必要があるのかと 考え続けたからです
Is that really important for my career?
それは本当に私の経歴で重要なことなのか?
Why did they need to know that I was transitioning careers or
他の人たちは 私が転職をしようとしているとか
that I was new to this industry?
この業界になじみがないとか知る必要があるのか?
I was at the event, doesn't that mean I was already interested?
イベントに参加していたのだから とっくに興味があったということではないのか?
This experience taught me that if I wanted to sound confident and
この経験から学んだことは 自信があるように見せ うまく伝えたいのなら 自分が何をしたいのか
communicate well, I needed a concise elevator pitch that showed what I wanted
なぜしたいのかを示す 簡潔なエレベータピッチが
and why I wanted it.
必要だということでした
My elevator pitch now is,
私の今のエレベータピッチはこうです
I'm a project manager passionate about personalized education.
私はプロジェクトマネージャーで 個別化教育にとても興味を持っています
After working in non-profits and public policy,
非営利団体や公共機関で 働いてから
I believe lifelong learning is the solution to many societal issues.
生涯学習が多くの社会的問題の 解決策であると信じるようになりました
I'm excited to apply my teaching and management skills at Udacity.
Udacity で私の指導スキルと管理スキルを 生かせるようがんばりたいです
So, let's dive in to how to develop an elevator pitch with personal branding in
では パーソナルブランディングを心に留めて エレベータピッチを組み立てる方法を
mind.
見ていきましょう